ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4156
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files
1968-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Miller, J. Gormly
Harper, Shirley
/4156
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8017037
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 04, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4108: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4145: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4172: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
Arrangement
Series I: Subject Files
Series II: Personnel Files
Harper, Shirley F.; Miller, J. Gormly; Martin P. Catherwood Library; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Library; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
8017037
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Academic Press Inc. - Allen and Union, Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Management Society - ARL, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arrow Electronics - The University of Newcastle, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Books From X to Z - Ballen Booksellers International Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - James Bennett Library Services - Bernan-Unipub, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - BRS - Blackwell's, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - BNA Books - R. R. Bowker, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Brodart Company - Butterworths, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Communications Workers of America - CUE/NAM, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Christian Labour Association of Canada - Canada Law Book Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Canadian Government Public Centre - Commerce Clearing House Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Committee For Economic Development - Facilities and Business Operations, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Libraries folder 1, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University Libraries folder 2, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University Libraries folder 3, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Libraries folder 4, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University Libraries folder 5, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - C. U. Stores Enterprises folder 1, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - C. U. Stores Enterprises folder 2, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - C. U. Stores Enterprises folder 3, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - C. U. Stores Enterprises folder 4, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - C. U. Stores Enterprises folder 5, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Coutts Library Services Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Coutts Library Services Inc. - Crown Publications Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Arnold Busck Boghandel - Dow Jones and Co. Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - E+I Cooperative Service Inc. - European Community Information Service, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Executive Telecom System Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Film Inc. - Federal Express Corp., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Fernandez Gatell Inc. - Gale Research Company, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gale Research Company - Greenwood Press Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Shirley F. Harper - Harvard Institute of Economic Research, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Alexander Hamilton Institute Incorporated - Hollinger Corporation, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - International Occupational Safety and Health Info. Ctr. - Information Access Company, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - IBM Corporation, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Interdepartmental Order folder 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Interdepartmental Order folder 2, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Interdepartmental Order folder 1, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Interdepartmental Order folder 2, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Interdepartmental Order folder 3, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Insights Video Productions - Input Culture Company, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Input Culture Co. folder 1, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Input Culture Co. folder 2, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Input Culture Co. folder 3, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans - International Social Security Association, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - James Publishing Inc. - Journal Voucher, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Journal Voucher, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - KLBS Archival Products - Labor Research Association, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - The Lawyers Co-operative Publishing Co. - Maine Dept. of Labor, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Olivia Mitchell - Michigan State University, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mead Data Central - MIT Sloan School, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - National Public Employer Labor Relations Association - National Safety Council, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research - New Zealand Government Printing Office, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Newsnet Inc. - Opinions Press, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Participatory Research Group - Public Affairs Information Service, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Queen's University Industrial Relations Centre - The Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Syma Systems Inc. - Richard Strassberg, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Science Associates/International Inc. - Society of American Archivists, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Simplex Time Recorder Co. - Statistics Canada, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Law Book Company - Triangle Book Shop Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - United Way of America - UNIPUB, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - United Nations - University Associates Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - University Microfilms International - The Urban Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Video Conversions International - Vu/Text Information Services Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Western Legal Publications - Women's Equity Action League, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Warren, Gorham, and Lamont Inc. - West Publishing Company, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - John Wiley and Sons Inc. - Yankee Book Peddler Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Series II: Personnel Files
  Scope and Contents
  RESTRICTED
  - Personnel Records: Part-Time and Temporary (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Paul Curry - Albany
  - Personnel Records: Part Time and Temporary (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Armstrong, Shannon, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    October 18, 1982 - February 15, 1984
  - Barnes, Jeffrey (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bunting, Helen - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Alanna - Personnel Records, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    August 28, 1980 - July 27, 1981
  - Keshishoglou, Barbara - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Landau, Margaret - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Ludington, Deborah (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Michaud, S. Diane (Lacey), 1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    June 1972 - April 1978, February 1981 - February 29, 1984
  - Minor, Beth - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Muse, Catherine P. - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Shaw, Rose Ann (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Way, Harold - Personnel Records, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Terminated April 15, 1983
  - Wilson, Nancy H. - Temp, Part-time (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Avakian, Leslie A. - Personnel Record (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Bailey, Bonnie A. - Personnel Record (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Brumsted, Julie - Personnel Record (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Inactive Personnel - Cosgrove, Colleen (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Cullen, Mary - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Danzig, Elizabeth Anne - Personnel Record (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Inactive Personnel - Ferro, Martha (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Goodrich, Gerald E. - Personnel File, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    September 7, 1988 - June 30, 1989
  - King, Ellen - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Koerpel, Gretchen - Personnel Record, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    November 1986 - August 2, 1989
  - Leary, Patricia - Personnel Records, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    March 19, 1984 - August 14, 1985
  - MacWilliams, Robert A. - Personnel Record (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Malone, Angela - Personnel Record, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    August 25, 1988 - November 29, 1989
  - Martin, Eileen - Personnel Records, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    March 19, 1984
  - Myers, Donald J. - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Personnel - Assistant Archivist (Michael Nash) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Randorf, Patricia - Personnel Record (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Reiger, Oya Yildirim - Personnel Records, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    February 12, 1987
  - Rose, Dora - Personnel Record (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Thomas, Terry - Personnel Records (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Wilson, Karen (Box 4, Folder 48)